Necib Intissar



- ™ spaceaurora50@gmail.com
 - +213674457459
- © +213674457459
- 🗘 triumph2525 🛚 Bē intissar necib

<u> </u>	
Arabic	
French	
English	

⟨⟨⟨ Interests⟩ ⟨ Interests

(1) Languages

Sports

- Fitness
- Yoga
- Bodybuilding
- Self defence...

■ Profile

An ambition, serious and hard-working person who admires the IT field with good experience in graphic and UX/UI design. Always perseveres to achieve the best results and is motivated to face new challenges to polish her skills and learn new experiences.

Skills	
PHP Laravel	
SQL MySql	
HTML/CSS Bootstrap	
ADOBE Illustrator, Photoshop, XI	
API Rest api	
POSTMAN API testing	
GIT Github	
Professional Experience	
Graphic Designer, NJNPUB ☑ 2020 – present Constantine, Algeria	

M.D in Computer Science, information system and web technology, University Abdelhamid Mehri Constantine 2 ☑ 2019 – 2021 | Constantine, Algeria

Education

B.D in Computer Science, information system, *University Abdelhamid Mehri* Constantine 2 ☑ 2016 – 2019 | Constantine, Algeria